Guide to the Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records, 1954-1998 and undated RL.01365
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1954-1998 and undated (Acc. 98-0396), 140 boxes
  - Video and Film
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs) (continued) (Box 5)
      - AST 96. ASPC--Liquidate It. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
      - AST 97. Plus Cold Medicine--The Phenomenal Fizz. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
      - AST 98. Plus--Drink. Circa 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
      - AST 99. Plus--3 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:15 (Box 5)
      - AST 100. Master--14 spots. 1990. TRT: 6:00 (Box 5)
      - ASP 101. ASPCM--When You Gotta Keep Going. 1990. TRT: :15 (Box 5)
      - AST 102. Plus--Phenominal Fizz Crwal (sic). 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
      - AST 103. Plus--Phenomenal Fizz Crawl Rev. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 5)
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs) (continued) (Box 6)
      - AST 104. 4 spots. 1990. TRT: 2:00 (Box 6)
      - AST 105. 2 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 6)
      - AST 106. Plumber. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 6)
      - AST 107. Fizzical Fitness. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 6)
      - AST 108. 3 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 6)
      - AST 109. Explosion. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 6)
      - AST 110. Pass it On. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 6)
      - AST 111. Fizzical Fitness ( Master). 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 6)
      - AST 112. Explosion Rev. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 6)
      - AST 113. Cincinnati Fast. 1990. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 6)
      - AST 114. Three Medicines (Drawings). 1990. TRT: :15 (Box 6)
      - AST 115. Drawings Rev 1. 1990. TRT: :15 (Box 6)
      - AST 116. In a Word/ How Would You Feel--Alt. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 6)
      - AST 117. Three Medicines Rev. 1990. TRT: :15 (Box 6)
      - AST 118. 3 spots-- all Relief. 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 6)
      - AST 119. 2 spots--both Drawings Rev. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 6)
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs) (continued) (Box 7)
      - AST 120. Lightening. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 7)
      - AST 121. Fireman Rev. B. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 7)
      - AST 122. Old Man Winter. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 7)
      - ASP 123. 2 spots--both Fireman. 1990. TRT: :45 (Box 7)
      - ASP 124. Fireman Rev 2B. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 7)
      - AST 125. 3 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 7)
      - AST 126. A Plus. 1990. TRT: :31 (Box 7)
      - AST 127. 4 spots--Everest & Rig. 1991. TRT: 1:30 (Box 7)
      - AST 128. Pour. 1991. TRT: :15 (Box 7)
      - AST 129. Purple Box. 1991. TRT: :15 (Box 7)
      - AST 130. Rig/Revised. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 7)
      - AST 131. 4 spots--Rig Rev 2 & Everest Rev. 1991. TRT: 1:30 (Box 7)
      - AST 132. Rig Rev. III Sinus Allergy Tag. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 7)
      - AST 133. 2 spots. 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 7)
      - AST 134. 2 spots. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 7)
      - AST 135. 4 spots all revised. 1992. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 7)
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs) (continued) (Box 8)
      - AST 136. 4 spots--opening frame, end scene with title dissolve, end scene without title for each (with address track time code). 1992. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 8)
      - AST 137. 3 spots. 1992. TRT: :45 (Box 8)
      - AST 138. 3 spots--all Dockworkers. 1992. TRT: 1:15 (Box 8)
      - AST 139. Dockworkers w/ Supers Rev 2. 1992. TRT: :15 (Box 8)
      - AST 140. 2 spots--both Dockworkers Rev. 1992. TRT: :15 (Box 8)
      - AST 141. Lawnmower Rev. 1992. TRT: :15 (Box 8)
      - AST 142. Dockworkers w/ Supers Rev 2. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 8)
      - AST 143. 2 spots--both Keith. 1992. TRT: :15 (Box 8)
      - AST 143A. Keith. 1992. TRT: :15 (Box 8)
      - AST 144. Dockworkers w/ Super Rev 3. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 8)
      - AST 145. 6 spots--all Cameraman Demo. 1992. TRT: 1:45 (Box 8)
      - AST 146. Cameraman Demo Alt. Rev. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 8)
      - AST 147. 2 spots. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 8)
      - AST 148. 2 spots--both Effervescent People. 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 8)
      - Miles Lab Off-Air Clips Alka Seltzer. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 8)
      - Unfinished Lunch. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 8)
    - Alka Seltzer (Miles Labs) (continued) (Box 9)
      - Plus Master Reel--New Book. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 9)
      - Alka 2. Alka 2 Master Reel. 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 9)
      - Misc. 1. 2 Alka Seltzer spots, plus a BIC spot. 1977. TRT: Circa 1:30 (Box 9)
      - Misc. 52. Stomach (No matter what shape your stomachs in). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 9)
      - Misc. 46. Stomach Montage. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 9)
      - Misc. 55. Unfinished Lunch. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 9)
      - Historical Reel--Alka-Seltzer Plop, Plop Campaign 31 commercials--handwritten list on cover. 1979. TRT: Circa 15:00 (Box 9)
      - AS I. Alka Seltzer Reel I--28 spots--rundown enclosed. 1974. TRT: 16:18 (Box 9)
      - AS II. Alka Seltzer Reel II--33 spots (28-60) --rundown enclosed. 1974. TRT: Circa 20:00 (Box 9)
      - AS III. Alka Seltzer Reel III--64 spots (61-124) --rundown enclosed. Undated. TRT: Circa 33:30 (Box 9)
      - AS IV. Alka Seltzer R IV--38 spots--rundown enclosed. Undated. TRT: Circa 22:00 (Box 9)
      - AS V. Alka Seltzer R V--15 spots--rundown enclosed. 1976. TRT: Circa 9:00 (Box 9)
      - AS VI. Alka Seltzer Master Reel VI New Book--handwritten list-- enclosed indicates 59 spots. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 9)
      - AS VII. Alka Seltzer Master Reel VII--no rundown. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 9)
      - Misc. 6. Alka Seltzer--Drug Abuse. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 9)
    - Amaretto
      - It's Like Love--Casino Vision. 1980. TRT: :30 (Box 9)
    - Atari (Box 10)
      - 1. Master Reel #1 (list enclosed). 1982-1983. TRT: Circa 23:00 (Box 10)
      - R-2. Master Reel R-2 (list enclosed). 1983-1984. TRT: Circa 23:00 (Box 10)
      - 28. Fun Club Revisions for each channel. 1983. TRT: :30 plus (Box 10)
      - 36. 6 spots. 1984. TRT: 3:00 (Box 10)
    - [Benson & Hedges: see Phillip Morris, box 86] (Box 10)
    - [BIC: see box 11] (Box 10)
    - Boost (Bristol Myers)
      - 1. Perfect Snack. 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 10)
      - 2. Perfect Snack. 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 10)
      - 3. Perfect Snack/ Donut Guy. 1996. TRT: :15 (Box 10)
      - 4. Perfect Snack/ Coffee Guy. 1996. TRT: :15 (Box 10)
      - 5. Perfect Snack. 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 10)
      - 6. Perfect Snack--The Sequel. 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 10)
      - 7. Perfect Snack--The Sequel Rev. 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 10)
      - 8. 6 spots--Boost Storyboard Presentation. Circa 1997. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 10)
      - 9. Anthem Two. 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 10)
      - 10. Anthem Two Rev. 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 10)
      - 11. Morphing Can (animatic). 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 10)
      - 12. 3 spots. 1997. TRT: 1:30 (Box 10)
      - 13. Anthem--New Flavors. 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 10)
    - [Bonanza: see box 112] (Box 10)
    - BIC (Box 11)
      - 1. 3 spots. Undated. TRT: 1:30 (Box 11)
      - 2. 2 spots (rough cuts). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 11)
      - 3. Stroke/ USA. 1976. TRT: :30 (Box 11)
      - 5. 2 spots (NG Vo's & slop) --mono, B& W. 1976. TRT: Circa 1:30 (Box 11)
      - Misc. 50. BIC Seminar Reel (16 Trf). 1981. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 11)
      - Misc. 53. 9 spots. 1982. TRT: Circa 6:00 (Box 11)
      - Reel I. Master Reel I--New Book (list enclosed--54 spots. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 11)
      - Reel 2. Master Reel 2-- (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 11)
      - BIC Air. BIC Show Promos (Circa 30 spots--mostly celebrities). 1976. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 11)
      - BIC Air. BIC Show Promos (Circa 30 spots--mostly celebrities) (last 2 look like duplicates). 1976. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 11)
    - Braniff Airlines
      - Master. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 11)
      - 2. 7 spots. 1979. TRT: 3:30 (Box 11)
      - 3. 8 spots. 1979. TRT: 4:00 (Box 11)
      - 8A. 8 spots. 1980. TRT: 5:30 (Box 11)
      - 9. QBCR 9453 thru QBCR 9843 *plus QBCR 9953. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 11)
      - 10. 11 spots (see Misc. 21--2 Braniff spots). 1980. TRT: 6:00 (Box 11)
    - Bonanza (Box 12)
      - Historical--handwritten note included. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 12)
    - Bristol Myers (list in box)
      - Boost (1-13) (see box 9). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 12)
      - 1. Clairol--Totally Organic. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 12)
      - 2. Clairol--3 spots--all Totally Organic. 1995. TRT: 1:30 (Box 12)
      - 3. Clairol--Totally Organic. 1995. TRT: :15 (Box 12)
      - 4. Clairol--2 spots--both Airplane. 1996. TRT: :45 (Box 12)
      - 5. Clairol--2 spots. 1996. TRT: :45 (Box 12)
      - 6. Clairol--6 spots--all Black Book (include Spanish & French). 1997. TRT: 2:30 (Box 12)
      - 7. Herbal Essence--2 spots--both Airplane. 1997. TRT: :45 (Box 12)
      - 8. Herbal Essence--Graduate. Circa 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 12)
      - Herbal Essence--Compilation reel 14 spots. 1997. TRT: 5:45 (Box 12)
      - 1. Hydrience-- Breakthrough. 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 12)
      - 2. Hydrience--Breakthrough Revised. 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 12)
      - 3. Hydrience--Breakthrough/ International. 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 12)
      - 4. Hydrience--Breakthrough. 1996. TRT: :15 (Box 12)
      - 6. Hydrience--4 spots--all Breakthrough includes UK. 1997. TRT: 1:25 (Box 12)
      - 2. Corporate--1. Cancer Cure (w/ Wish Well tag), 2. Amazing Body (oncology), 3. Cancer Cure (w/ Can't Wait tag). 1997. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 12)
      - 1. Natural Instincts-- If Your Hair Could Talk. 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 12)
    - Bristol Myers (continued) (Box 13)
      - 2. Natural Instincts--Leslie / Makeover. 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
      - 3. Natural Instincts--3 spots. 1197. TRT: 1:30 (Box 13)
      - 4. Natural Instincts--Elevator/ U.S./ Aloe tag Revised. 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
      - 1. Vagistat--4 spots. 1997. TRT: 1:30 (Box 13)
      - 2. Vagistat--Absolutely It Works rev. 1997. TRT: :45 (Box 13)
      - 3. Vagistat--2 spots. 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
      - 4. Vagistat--Absolutely It Works, Two Women rev. 1997. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
    - Britannia Sportswear
      - 1. 2 spots tied. 1979. TRT: 1:00 (Box 13)
      - 2. 3 spots (see inside log). 1980. TRT: 1:15 (Box 13)
      - 3. 1 animatic spot-- (Do you see those girls?). 1980. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
    - Cadbury Beverages
      - 1. Canada Dry Flavored Seltzers--Life in a Bubble. Circa 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
      - 2. Canada Dry Ginger Ale--Relaxation. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
      - 3. Canada Dry Ginger Ale-- Woman. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
      - 4. Canada Dry Ginger Ale--Relaxation/ Rev. I. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
      - 5. Canada Dry Ginger Ale--Women/ Rev/. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 13)
    - Cadbury Beverages (continued) (Box 14)
      - 6. Canada Dry Seltzer--Life in a Bubble Revised. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 14)
      - 7. Canada Dry Seltzer Life in a Bubble Rev DMCC. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 14)
      - 8. Cadbury Schweppes Sunkist--3 spots. 1987. TRT: 1:30 (Box 14)
      - 9. Sunkist Soft Drinks Inc. Orange soda--4 spots. 1987. TRT: 2:00 (Box 14)
      - 10. Sunkist Soft Drinks Inc. Orange soda--2 spots. 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 14)
      - 11. Canada Dry Ginger Ale--3 holiday spots. 1987. TRT: 1:30 (Box 14)
      - 11A. Cadbury Schweppes--Canada Dry Ginger Ale--3 holiday spots. 1987. TRT: 1:30 (Box 14)
      - 12. Sunkist Soft Drinks Inc. Orange soda--A.Introduction, b. Drink in the Sun Animatic x2. Circa 1988. TRT: 6:40 (Box 14)
      - 12A. Cadbury Beverage/ Sunkist--Drink in the Sun Animatic. 1988. TRT: Circa :30 (Box 14)
      - 13. Cadbury Canada Dry--Canada Dry Sparklers Flavor Experience. Circa 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 14)
      - 14. Cadbury/ Schweppes--Drink in the Sun dealer version. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 14)
      - 15. Cadbury Schweppes--Canada Dry Ginger Ale--2 spots. 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 14)
      - 16. Cadbury Schweppes--Canada Dry Ginger Ale--6 spots. 1988. TRT: 3:00 (Box 14)
      - 17. Cadbury Schweppes Sunkist Orange Soda--2 spots. 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 14)
      - 18. Cadbury Schweppes Sunkist Orange Soda--1 spot. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 14)
      - 19. Cadbury Canada Dry--Musicians (Box). 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 14)
    - Cadbury Beverages (continued) (Box 15)
      - 20. Canada Dry Ginger Ale--Fireplace. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 15)
      - 21. Cadbury Schweppes Canada Dry Ginger Ale--Musicians revised. Circa 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 15)
      - 22. Sunkist--3 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:30 (Box 15)
      - 23. Cadbury Schweppes--Surf City/ Diet tag. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 15)
      - 24. Canada Dry Ginger Ale--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 15)
      - 25. Cadbury Schweppes Sunkist--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 15)
      - 26. Cadbury Schweppes Sunkist Diet--Three Suns/ Diet tag. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 15)
    - Cadbury Candy
      - York Skier. Cadbury Peter Paul/ York Peppermint Patties--2 spots. 1987. TRT: :45 (Box 15)
      - 6A. Cadbury Creme & Mini Eggs. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 15)
      - 8A. Cadbury Schweppes Sunkist. 1987. TRT: 1:30 (Box 15)
      - 8A. Cadbury Schweppes Sunkist. 1987. TRT: 1:30 (Box 15)
      - . Cadbury Candy Master Reel (no list of contents). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 15)
      - DFS. Cadbury Mounds/ Almond Joy--Historical Reel--27 spots--list inside. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 15)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank
      - 1. Chase Master Reel #1. Circa 1981. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 15)
      - 6. Chase St. Andrea Show. 1981. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 15)
      - 6A. Chase St. Andrea Show (either duplicate or continuation). 1981. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 15)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank (continued) (Box 16)
      - 8. Chase Master--14 spots. 1981. TRT: 7:40 (Box 16)
      - 13. Chase Manhattan Bank presentation. 1981. TRT: 1:15 (Box 16)
      - 15. Chase Manhattan Retail--Confusion Rev. I. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 16)
      - 16. Chase Manhattan Retail--Chase You're On. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 16)
      - 17. Chase Manhattan--Money Market 11% Rev. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 16)
      - 24. Chase Manhattan Celebration CD--Father of the Bride. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 16)
      - . Chase Manhattan Television--Compilation tape--58 spots (list enclosed). Undated. TRT: 31:00 plus (Box 16)
    - Citibank
      - Historical Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 16)
      - Master #1. Citibank Historical Reel 16mm transfer. 1970-1976. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 16)
      - Master #2. Citibank Master #2. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 16)
      - R-3. Citibank Master R-3. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 16)
      - R-4. Citibank Master R-4. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 16)
      - R-5. Citibank Master R-5 Comp, Reel (list inside). 1979. TRT: Circa 16:30 (Box 16)
      - R-6Citibank Master R-6. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 16)
      - Citibank--Jim Adkins 5/19/77. 1977. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 16)
      - Citibank--Jim Adkins 6/6/77. 1977. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 16)
      - Compilation Reel-- (list inside--13 spots). Undated. TRT: 10:00 (Box 16)
    - Citgo (Box 17)
      - Nature. 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 17)
    - Citizen Watch
      - Master Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 17)
    - Columbia Pictures
      - Master Reel (list enclosed). 1978-1979. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 17)
    - Continental Airlines
      - 10. Air to Air Photography Visual time code. 1990. TRT: 23:30 (Box 17)
      - 17. Continental Air to Air Photography 91. 1991. TRT: 2:30 (Box 17)
      - 18. Continental Air to Air Photography 91. 1991. TRT: 1:15 (Box 17)
      - 23. Continental Airlines Domestic--6 spots. 1991. TRT: 3:00 (Box 17)
      - 31. Continental--10 spots. 1992. TRT: 2:30 (Box 17)
      - 33. Continental Airlines--10 spots. 1992. TRT: 2:30 (Box 17)
      - 33A. Continental Airlines--10 spots. 1992. TRT: 2:20 (Box 17)
      - 41. Continental Airlines--Part 1 Air to Air Footage w/ Regen address track T.C. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 17)
      - 41A. Continental Airlines--Air to Air Footage (film transfer Master 2/25/93) Part 1 w/ Regen Visual Time Code. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 17)
      - 42. Continental Airlines--Part 2 Air to Air Footage w/ Regen address track T.C. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 17)
      - 42A. Continental Airlines--Air to Air Footage (film transfer Master 2/25/93) Part 2 w/ Regen Visual Time Code. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 17)
      - 47. Continental IBP--3 spots. 1992. TRT: 1:25 (Box 17)
      - 56. Continental Airlines Domestic--Shrinking Ticket (18 versions see enclosed). 1993. TRT: 3:00 (Box 17)
    - Continental Airlines (continued) (Box 18)
      - R-1. Continental Air Master R-1. Circa 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 18)
      - R-2. Continental Air Master R-2. Circa 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 18)
      - R-3. Continental Air Master R-3. Circa 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 18)
    - Continental Baking
      - Master Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 18)
    - Council on Family Health
      - 1. Bedroom. 1978. TRT: :30 (Box 18)
      - 2. Council on Family Health--Bedroom Rev. 1979. TRT: :20 (Box 18)
      - 3. Council on Family Health--6 spots. 1982. TRT: 2:00 (Box 18)
      - 4. Council on Family Health--2 spots. 1982. TRT: :20 (Box 18)
      - 5. Council on Family Health--4 spots. 1984. TRT: 2:50 (Box 18)
      - 6. Council on Family Health--Surgeon. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 18)
      - 7. Council on Family Health--2 spots. 1987. TRT: :40 (Box 18)
    - Cosmair
      - Master. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 18)
    - Dallas Civic Opera
      - 1. Dallas Civic Opera--3 spots. Undated. TRT: :50 (Box 18)
      - 2. Dallas Civic Opera--Hagman A, Hagman B. 1980. TRT: 20:00 (Box 18)
      - 3. Dallas Civic Opera--5 spots. 1981. TRT: 1:10 (Box 18)
    - Datsun Dealers
      - Composition Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 18)
    - Deleal (Miles Labs) (Box 19)
      - 1. Deleal--Not One Summer Older. 1980. TRT: :30 (Box 19)
      - 2. Deleal--Younger Man. 1980. TRT: :30 (Box 19)
    - Diners Club
      - Master #1. Master Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 19)
      - Master #2. Patrick O'Neal Signature Magazine. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 19)
    - Dun & Bradstreet
      - 1. For Agency Reels--M. Moore--We See Master. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 19)
      - 2 (2 copies). We See Rev 2 use for agency reels. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 19)
      - 3. We See Too. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 19)
    - Dungarees
      - 2 spots. Undated. TRT: 1:30 (Box 19)
    - Fieldcrest
      - 1. Domestic Towels--Towels. 1978. TRT: :30 (Box 19)
      - 2. Sheets/Towels--14 spots. 1979. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 19)
      - 3. Fieldcrest--2 spots--Bath/ Fine Store Generic Everywhere. Circa 1979. TRT: 1:00 (Box 19)
    - Fleischmann
      - #1. Master Reel #1. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 19)
      - #2. Master Reel #2. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 19)
    - [Ford Motor: see box 20] (Box 19)
    - Gallo
      - Composition Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 19)
    - GAP
      - Master reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 19)
    - Ford Motor Company (Box 20)
      - 1. Corporate--Incredible Tour--Las Vegas Film. 1979. TRT: 4:00 (Box 20)
      - 2. Corporate--Better Ideas in Manufacturing Commercials (list enclosed--23 spots). Circa 1979. TRT: 16:21 plus (Box 20)
      - 3. Corporate--7 spots. 1979. TRT: 7:30 (Box 20)
      - 4. Corporate--Incredible Tour--Rev. II. 1979. TRT: 1:00 (Box 20)
      - 5. Corporate--2 spots. 1979. TRT: 2:00 (Box 20)
      - 6. Corporate--Trucks/ Rev. 1979. TRT: 1:00 (Box 20)
      - 7. Corporate--3 spots. 1980. TRT: 2:00 (Box 20)
      - 8. Corporate--2 spots. 1980. TRT: 2:00 (Box 20)
      - 9. Corporate--Fairmont / Zephyr--Rebate--Ver II. 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 20)
      - 10. Ford Corporate--Photomatic--8 spots. 1980. TRT: Circa 8:00 (Box 20)
      - 11 (2 copies). Corporate--4 spots. 1980. TRT: 4:00 (Box 20)
      - 12. Corporate--4 spots. 1980. TRT: 4:00 (Box 20)
      - 13. Fairmont--2 spots. 1980. TRT: 2:00 (Box 20)
      - 14. Fairmont--2 spots. Circa 1980. TRT: 2:00 (Box 20)
      - 15. Fairmont--Gas Station, Chorus. 1980. TRT: 1:00 (Box 20)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 21)
      - 16. Corporate--4 spots. 1981. TRT: 4:00 (Box 21)
      - 17. Corporate--4 spots. 1981. TRT: 4:00 (Box 21)
      - 18. Granada/ Cougar, Revised. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 21)
      - 19. Ford Knows Sally. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 21)
      - 20. Gas Station. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 21)
      - 21. Ford Knows Bob. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 21)
      - 22. Ford Knows America Omnibus (test spot). 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 21)
      - 23. Ford Lincoln Mercury--2 spots. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 21)
      - 24. Ford Knows Sally. 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 21)
      - 25. Corporate--2 spots. 1981. TRT: 2:00 (Box 21)
      - 26. Corporate--2 spots. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 21)
      - 27. Corporate--Quality 1--Pride. 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 21)
      - 28. Quality 1--Hands On Rev (This tape has a pop in the final scene). 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 21)
      - 29. Quality 1--Employe (sic) Involvement. 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 21)
      - 30. Corporate--3 spots. 1981. TRT: 1:30 (Box 21)
      - 33. Q1 Series II. 1982. TRT: 1:30 (Box 21)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 22)
      - 34. Q1 Series II--6 spots. 1981. TRT: 3:00 (Box 22)
      - 35. Q1 Series II-- Door Fit Rev. I. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 22)
      - 36. Q1 Series II--Wind Noise & Water Leaks Rev. 2. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 22)
      - 37. Q1 Series II--3 spots. 1982. TRT: 1:30 (Box 22)
      - 38. Corporate--Satellite. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 22)
      - 39. Reputation--Alternative Fuels. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 22)
      - 41. Image--Overseas (Disclaimer IV on Air Version. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 22)
      - 43. Renaissance Corporate 2 test spots. 1982. TRT: 1:00 (Box 22)
      - 44. Corporate--2 spots. 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 22)
      - 45. Maysles Films Inc.--Ford Film Quality is Job 1. 1981. TRT: 2:30 (Box 22)
      - 46. Corporate--No Other Company. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 22)
      - 47. Ford Corporate--We're Ready. 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 22)
      - 48. Corporate--4 spots. 1983. TRT: 2:30 (Box 22)
      - 49. Corporate--2 spots. 1983. TRT: 2:00 (Box 22)
      - 50. Corporate--4 spots. 1983. TRT: 2:30 (Box 22)
      - 51. Ford--We're Ready Rev #2. 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 22)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 23)
      - 52. Corporate--4 spots. 1983. TRT: 2:30 (Box 23)
      - 53. Corporate-- We're Ready Rev III. 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 23)
      - 54. Ford--What The People Said. 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 23)
      - 55. Ford-What The People Said Rev. 1. 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 23)
      - 56. Corporate Seasonal--Jackie Stewart Seat Belt. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 23)
      - 57. Corporate--Comparison II/ Title Rev. 1. 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 23)
      - 58. Corporate--2 spots. 1984. TRT: 1:30 (Box 23)
      - 59. Corporate--3 spots. Circa 1984. TRT: 1:30 (Box 23)
      - 60. Q1--5 spots. 1984. TRT: 3:00 (Box 23)
      - 61. Ford--2 spots. 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 23)
      - 62. Ford Corporate--So Big Rev II. 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 23)
      - 63. Ford Corporate--Mileage Rev. 1. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 23)
      - 64. Ford Corporate--Shine--Rev II. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 23)
      - 65. Corporate--So Many Parts. 1984. TRT: 1:30 (Box 23)
      - 66. Corporate--2 spots. 1984. TRT: :40 (Box 23)
      - 67. Corporate--2 spots. Circa 1984. TRT: :40 (Box 23)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 24)
      - 68. Corporate--4 spots. 1985. TRT: 3:00 (Box 24)
      - 69. 3 spots. 1985. TRT: 2:00 (Box 24)
      - 70. Corporate--Quality Survey. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
      - 71. 3 spots. 1985. TRT: 2:30 (Box 24)
      - 72. Ford Motor Company--Ergonomics. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 24)
      - 73. Ford Motor Company--Acceleration Deceleration. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 24)
      - 74. Ford Motor Company--3 spots. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 24)
      - 75. Corporate--Quality Survey Rev. I. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
      - 76. Corporate--2 spots. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
      - 77. Ford Motor Company--See Through Rev. ABC. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 24)
      - 78. Ford Motor Company--See Through Rev. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 24)
      - 79. Corporate--2 spots. 1986. TRT: :40 (Box 24)
      - 80. Ford--3 spots. 1986. TRT: 1:30 (Box 24)
      - 81. Ford--3 spots. 1986. TRT: 1:30 (Box 24)